<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Lomorage</title><link>http://lomorage.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Lomorage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 08:17:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://lomorage.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploy NPS tunnel service on fly.io for Lomorage remote access</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2022/10/14/flyio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 08:17:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2022/10/14/flyio/</guid><description>What is NPS NPS is a tunnel service similar with Ngrok, it&amp;rsquo;s a reverse proxy used to access local service behind the NAT/Firewall. If you are running self-hosted service like Lomorage at home, and you are outside and want to access Lomorage, then you can use NPS.
However NPS need to run somewhere with public access, there are lots of service providers there, fly.io has a free plan without binding any credit card, and it supports docker deployment, and the servers runs in datacenters around the world so that the service can be deployed close to the users.</description></item><item><title>PhotoPrism meets Lomorage: The best Google Photos alternative</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2022/02/11/photoprism/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2022/02/11/photoprism/</guid><description>&lt;p>PhotoPrism is an Open Source AI Photo Management tool, and it works very well along with Lomorage.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Small image compression size comparison between Jpeg and Webp</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2021/09/01/piq-size/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 21:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2021/09/01/piq-size/</guid><description>Motivation Lomorage is free private photo cloud solution that puts you in control of your photos and videos. To get best user experience among different platforms, such as iOS, Android, web, it utilizes smaller size thumbnail image to allow the clients to load image faster initially.
At the same time, unlike desktop applications, mobile clients have limited storage, and a good mobile application should take it into consideration and provide better user experience while require system resources as little as possible.</description></item><item><title>Turn your old android tablet to lomorage photo frame</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2021/08/26/zero-cost-android-frame/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 10:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2021/08/26/zero-cost-android-frame/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have and old android tablet at home, how to turn it to as photo frame to display my pictures?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Run Lomoage Docker in Windows 10</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/11/16/windows-docker/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 22:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/11/16/windows-docker/</guid><description>&lt;p>Though Lomorage already provide Windows Native MSI package, But if you like to run Docker image in Windows, please follow below steps to do so. Esp. on Windows Server, Docker can leverage the Windows HYPER-v technology，and let the Lomorage running faster. If you do not know what is Docker, you also can download the native Lomorage installer for Windows, &lt;a href="https://lomorage.com/zh/installation-win/">Download Lomorage Windows Installer&lt;/a>。&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Move MyCloud to Lomorage</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/05/17/import_my_cloud/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/05/17/import_my_cloud/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>I&lt;/strong> have ever bought one MyCloud 6T storage to save my photos and videos, but you know, the
My Cloud app is not good to use, so everything I have to connect to my phone with USB cable, and
keep the computer on to copy the files to MyCloud disk.
&lt;strong>Now&lt;/strong> let me introduce how to import / move MyCloud data to Lomorage.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Setup Covid-19 dashboard using Raspberry Pi</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 22:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</guid><description>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s hard time for everyone, covid-19 is spreading the world, even though you can easily getting the news on your finger tips, it still helpful to setup a dedicated dashboard to show the statistics and relating news of covid-19. The following gives step by step guide to customize your covid-19 dashboard using Raspberry Pi.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Setup Lomorage secondary backup with Raspberry Pi</title><link>http://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</guid><description>&lt;p>Photos and video are valuable assets, having a single backup is not enough, we at least should have secondary backup besides the primary backup, and ideally one more remote backup. Lomorage currently provide the option to setup a secondary backup. There are several options to do this.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://lomorage.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/contact/</guid><description>We are here to help you Report problems, having new requirements? we are glad to hear from you, that will help us to polish the products.
You can also join our slack channel.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>http://lomorage.com/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/faq/</guid><description>How comes the name &amp;ldquo;Lomorage&amp;rdquo;? What is the cost of Lomorage? How to setup redundancy backup? What file systems supported? Why folders named with date time seem not correct on hard drive? How to setup a secondary backup? Does Lomorage support backup edited file? What is background backup? How to recover from Raspbian boot failure? I forget password, how to reset? What can it do besides photo backup and management?</description></item><item><title>Price Comparison</title><link>http://lomorage.com/compare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/compare/</guid><description>Price Comparison The following comparison only considered the biggest selling point for each category, and assuming the main purpose is photo backup and photo management, so if you need more than that, just go with NAS, or get Orange Pi Zero or other single board computer to DIY yourself if you are expert.
We are not against cloud storage, it can be as good backup for local storage, and we suggest user keep the local copy.</description></item><item><title>Survey</title><link>http://lomorage.com/survey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://lomorage.com/survey/</guid><description>loading…</description></item></channel></rss>