<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lomorage</title>
    <link>https://lomorage.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lomorage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 22:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://lomorage.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Covid-19 dashbaord using Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 22:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s hard time for everyone, covid-19 is spreading the world, even though you can easily getting the news on your finger tips, it still helpful to setup a dedicated dashboard to show the statistics and relating news of covid-19. The following gives step by step guide to customize your covid-19 dashboard using Raspberry Pi.
s  Table of Contents  Table of Contents Prepare How it works Installation  1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Lomorage secondary backup with Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Photos and video are valuable assets, having a single backup is not enough, we at least should have secondary backup besides the primary backup, and ideally one more remote backup. Lomorage currenlty provide the option to setup a secondary backup. There are several options to do this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/external-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/external-access/</guid>
      <description>External Access Configuration Currently, external access need some manual setup and some technical background, we will make the process more user-friendly later.
There are a few tunnel services available for free use, most tunnel services require a client application running on your device, and set up a connection to the service running by the service provider, and it will give a subdomain name for you to use, if you access the URL with that subdomain, the tunnel service will forward the traffic/request to the client application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/install-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/install-frame/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents  Install lomo-frame Setup lomo-frame  Quickstart Turn Frame ON/OFF Stop/Start lomo-frame Service Schedule Frame ON/OFF time Playback Order Customize playlist Playback Media Type Keyboard control Setup multiple digital frame  1. Install lomo-frame 2. Setup WiFi connection 3. Check IP address of primary Raspberry Pi 4. Find the mount directory on primary Raspberry Pi 5. Mount on Raspberry Pi zero w 6. Reboot    Install lomo-frame If you install the latest Lomorage Raspberry Pi OS image, you should already have the lomo-frame application installed in that image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation-ios/</guid>
      <description>Install Lomorage iOS client You can install the application on either iPad or iPhone, the minimum iOS version required in 10.3.
  -- After launching Lomorage, it should be able to discover the Lomorage service running in the same network. If you have multiple Lomorage service instances running, those will be listed and you can choose one to use. If Lomorage service can&amp;rsquo;t be discovered automatically, you can discover the service via QRCode Scanning when using Windows or MacOS LomoAgent (open settings in LomoAgent to show the QRCode), or you can input the IP address and port manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation-osx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation-osx/</guid>
      <description>Install Lomorage Service on MacOS 1. Click the link below to download Lomorage Service Application.
macOS 2. Double click &amp;ldquo;LomoAgent.dmg&amp;rdquo; to start installation, and follow the steps below to finish the installation.
 3. Run LomoAgent Application，please allow network access for LomoAgent if firewall is triggered.
4. After launch the Lomorage application，You need to set the &amp;ldquo;Home directory&amp;rdquo; before using Lomorage，&amp;rdquo;Home directory&amp;rdquo; is used to save the photos and videos uploading from your phone。You can also set up a backup directory which served as redundancy backup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation-pi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation-pi/</guid>
      <description>Install Lomorage Service on Raspberry Pi To run on Raspberry Pi, you need to order a Raspberry Pi, we have tested the image the following models:
 Raspberry Pi 4 Model B Raspberry Pi 3 Model B+ Raspberry Pi Zero W Raspberry Pi 2 Model B  If you don&amp;rsquo;t have one yet, we would recommend the newer version, which gives better performance. The minimum set you need includes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation-web/</guid>
      <description>Install Lomorage Web client You can use Lomorage Web client to upload photos/videos from desktop/laptop using browser, and you can use the gallery to view the photos/videos stored in Lomorage.
If you are using Lomorage Service in MacOS, then you can just click &amp;ldquo;import&amp;rdquo; menu item in LomoAgent Application, and it will open the web application.
If you are using Lomorage Service in Raspberry Pi, then you can use the following command to install Lomorage Web client on your raspberry Pi:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation-win/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation-win/</guid>
      <description>Install Lomorage Service on Windows 1. Click the link below to download Lomorage Service Application.
Windows 2. double click &amp;ldquo;lomoagent.msi&amp;rdquo; to start installation. If Windows Defender shows &amp;ldquo;lomoagent.msi&amp;rdquo; as unknown application, please follow the steps below to allow it to run.
 3. Follow the wizzard to finish the installation, in the End-User License Agreement, please checked the box as below.
 4. Now you should see the lomoagent icon on your desktop, you can double click to start the lomoagent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Report problems, having new requirements? we are glad to hear from you, that will help us to polish the products.
You can also join our slack channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>1. How comes the name &amp;ldquo;Lomorage&amp;rdquo;? 2. Why another photo backup service? 3. How to setup redundancy backup? 4. What file systems supported? 5. Why the date time seems not correct? 6. How to set a secondary backup? 7. Does Lomorage support backup edited file? 8. What is background backup?  1. How comes the name &amp;ldquo;Lomorage&amp;rdquo;? If you know what Lomography is, then &amp;ldquo;Lomorage&amp;rdquo; is just a combination of &amp;ldquo;Lomography&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Storage&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feature Highlight</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/features/</guid>
      <description>--  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Privacy Matters Lomorage is a private cloud service which runs on your private network, which gives you the convenience of cloud-based photo backup service, but without the concern of leaking privacy. We are not, and will never collect ANY user privacy data.
You can also set up multiple Lomorage services in your private network, for different family members, which are completely isolated with each other.
&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Cross-Platform There is no OS limitation for running the Lomorage service, you can backup your photos on MAC, Windows and Raspberry Pi, and we will add other OS support upon user&amp;rsquo;s request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Guide</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation Guide 1. Overview To use Lomorage, you need to run the Lomorage service in your local network, either on Windows, OSX or Raspberry Pi. And then you need to download the client APP at the APP store. Once you run the Lomorage service, the client APP is supposed to find the service running automatically with zero configuration, then you can upload photos on the Phone.
2. Install Lomorage Service The first step is to set up the Lomorage service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>