<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lomorage</title>
    <link>https://lomorage.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lomorage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 22:43:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lomorage.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Run Lomoage Docker in Windows 10</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/11/16/windows-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 22:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/11/16/windows-docker/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Though Lomorage already provide Windows Native MSI package, But if you like to run Docker image in Windows, please follow below steps to do so. Esp. on Windows Server, Docker can leverage the Windows HYPER-v technology，and let the Lomorage running faster. If you do not know what is Docker, you also can download the native Lomorage installer for Windows, &lt;a href=&#34;https://lomorage.com/zh/installation-win/&#34;&gt;Download Lomorage Windows Installer&lt;/a&gt;。&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Move MyCloud to Lomorage</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/05/17/import_my_cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2020 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/05/17/import_my_cloud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I&lt;/strong&gt; have ever bought one MyCloud 6T storage to save my photos and videos, but you know, the
My Cloud app is not good to use, so everything I have to connect to my phone with USB cable, and
keep the computer on to copy the files to MyCloud disk.
&lt;strong&gt;Now&lt;/strong&gt; let me introduce how to import / move MyCloud data to Lomorage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Covid-19 dashboard using Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 22:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2020/03/29/covid19/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s hard time for everyone, covid-19 is spreading the world, even though you can easily getting the news on your finger tips, it still helpful to setup a dedicated dashboard to show the statistics and relating news of covid-19. The following gives step by step guide to customize your covid-19 dashboard using Raspberry Pi.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Lomorage secondary backup with Raspberry Pi</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 13:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/blog/2019/12/24/raspberrypi-hd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Photos and video are valuable assets, having a single backup is not enough, we at least should have secondary backup besides the primary backup, and ideally one more remote backup. Lomorage currently provide the option to setup a secondary backup. There are several options to do this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Report problems, having new requirements? we are glad to hear from you, that will help us to polish the products.
You can also join our slack channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/faq/</guid>
      <description>1. How comes the name &amp;ldquo;Lomorage&amp;rdquo;? 2. What is the cost of Lomorage? 3. What is the business model? 4. How to setup redundancy backup? 5. What file systems supported? 6. Why the date time seems not correct? 7. How to set a secondary backup? 8. Does Lomorage support backup edited file? 9. What is background backup? 10. How to recover from Raspbian boot failure? 11. I forget password, how to reset?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Price Comparison</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/compare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/compare/</guid>
      <description>Price Comparison The following comparison only considered the biggest selling point for each category, and assuming the main purpose is photo backup and photo management, so if you need more than that, just go with NAS, or get Orange Pi Zero or other single board computer to DIY yourself if you are expert.
We are not against cloud storage, it can be as good backup for local storage, and we suggest user keep the local copy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survey</title>
      <link>https://lomorage.com/survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lomorage.com/survey/</guid>
      <description>loading… </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
